<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCooknow</string>


    <string name="t1">
        Adobong Manok
    </string>
    <string name="e1">"2lbs chicken cut into serving pieces
3pcs dried bay leaves
8tbsp soy sauce
4tbsp white vinegar
5cloves garlic crushed
1and ½ cups water
3tbsp cooking oil
1tsp sugar
1/4tsp salt (optional)
1tsp whole peppercorn"
    </string>
    <string name="tr">
        Combine chicken, soy sauce, and garlic in a large bowl. Mix well\n
        Marinate the chicken for at least 1 hour. (Note: the longer the time, the better)\n
        Heat a cooking pot. Pour cooking oil\n
        When the oil is hot enough, pan-fry the marinated chicken for 2 minutes per side\n
        Pour-in the remaining marinade, including garlic. Add water. Bring to a boil\n
        Add dried bay leaves and whole peppercorn. Simmer for 30 minutes or until the chicken gets tender\n
        Add vinegar. Stir and cook for 10 minutes\n
        Put-in the sugar, and salt. Stir and turn the heat off. Serve hot\n
    </string>


    <string name="b">
        Tinolang Manok
    </string>
    <string name="b1">
"1whole chicken, cut into serving pieces
1/2pc small green papaya, cut into wedges
1tbsp garlic, chopped
1medium-sized onion, chopped
1ginger, sliced
1chicken broth cube
36oz rice washing
2tbsp fish sauce
3tbsp oil
hot pepper leaves
salt and pepper"
    </string>

    <string name="b2">
        Sauté the ginger, onion and garlic\n
Put-in the chicken and cook until color turns light brown\n
Pour-in the rice washing and fish sauce. Mix well and simmer for 45 minutes\n
Add the green papaya wedges and simmer for another 5 minutes\n
Finally, add salt, pepper, chicken broth cube and hot pepper leaves\n
Serve hot and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <!--> END </!-->

    <string name="c">
        Afritadang Manok
    </string>
    <string name="c1">
"1and ½ lbs chicken cut into serving pieces
2pcs potato cubed
1pc carrot sliced
8oz tomato sauce
3pcs hotdog sliced
1/2cup green peas
3pcs bay leaves
1pc red onion chopped
2tsp garlic minced
3cups chicken broth
1/2tsp sugar
3tbsp cooking oil
salt and ground black pepper to taste"
    </string>
    <string name="c2">
Heat the oil in a cooking pot. Saute onion and garlic until the onion softens\n
Add chicken. Cook for 30 seconds. Turn it over and cook the other side for another 30 seconds\n
Pour tomato sauce and chicken broth. Cover. Let boil\n
Add dried bay leaves. Cover the cooking pot. Continue to cook in medium heat for 30 minutes\n
Add hotdogs and carrot. Cook for 3 minutes\n
Add potato. Cover the pot and cook for 8 minutes\n
Add green peas. Cook for 2 minutes\n
Season with salt and ground black pepper\n
Serve\n
    </string>


    <string name="d">
        Creamy Chicken Pastel
    </string>
    <string name="d1">
"2lbs chicken breast cut into cubes
1pc Knorr Chicken Cube
1pc Chorizo de Bilbao sliced
4pcs hotdogs sliced
1pcs potato cubed
1pc carrot sliced
1pc red bell pepper sliced
1pc green bell pepper sliced
3/4cup button mushroom sliced
15oz all-purpose cream
1/4cup soy sauce
1pc lime
1pc onion chopped
4cloves garlic minced
3/4cup water
salt and ground black pepper to taste"
    </string>
    <string name="d2">
Combine chicken, soy sauce, and lime in a large bowl. Mix well. Marinate chicken for at least 30 minutes\n
Heat oil in a cooking pot. Saute onion and garlic\n
Once the onion softens, add the chorizo. Saute for 1 minute\n
Put chicken into the pot. Saute until the color turns light brown\n
Add water. Let boil\n
Add Knorr Chicken Cube. Stir. Cover and continue to cook for 20 minutes\n
Put the sliced hotdogs into the pot. Cook in medium heat until the liquid reduces to half\n
Add potato and carrot. Pour-in all-purpose cream. Cover and cook for 8 minutes\n
Stir-in the mushroom and bell peppers. Stir. Cook for 3 minutes\n
Season with ground black pepper and salt\n
Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with warm rice. Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="f">
    Asadong Manok
</string>
    <string name="f1">
"2lbs chicken cut into serving pieces
1/4cup lemon juice
2tbsp soy sauce
1/4cup butter
1and ½ cup of tomato sauce
1large onion diced
2pcs dried bay leaves
2large potatoes quartered
1/2tsp salt
1/2tsp ground black pepper
3/4cup cooking oil"
    </string>
    <string name="f2">
        Rub the chicken with salt and pepper and let stand for at least 30 minutes\n
Heat a frying pan then pour-in the cooking oil and Pan Fry the chicken. Set aside\n
Heat a cooking pot or wok then put-in the butter\n
When the butter is hot enough, add the onions and sauté until the texture becomes soft\n
Add-in the bay leaves and cook for a minute\n
Pour-in the tomato sauce and bring to a boil\n
Add the soy sauce and lemon juice then stir to ensure that the mixture is properly distributed and simmer for 5 to 7 minutes\n
Add the pan-fried chicken and simmer for 10 minutes\n
Place the potatoes in and continue to simmer for 7 to 12 minutes\n
Turn off the heat then transfer to a serving plate and serve\n
Share and enjoy\n
    </string>

    <!-->  </!-->


    <string name="g">Chicken Sopas</string>

    <string name="g1">
"12oz chicken breasts boneless
1/2pc cabbage sliced
3stalks celery chopped
1pc onion diced
3pcs hotdog sliced
3/4cups carrots diced
12oz evaporated milk
1and ½ cups elbow macaroni
2tsp minced garlic
1pc Knorr Chicken Cube
6to 8 cups water
3tbsp cooking oil
salt and ground black pepper to taste"
</string>
    <string name="g2">
Boil 3 cups water in a medium pot. Add the chicken breasts\n
Cover and cook in medium heat for 15 to 18 minutes. You may add more water if needed\n
Separate the chicken from the water. Let the chicken cool down and then shred. Set both shredded chicken and water aside\n
Heat oil in a large soup pot. Sauté the garlic until it turns medium brown. Add onion, celery, and carrot. Continue to sauté for 2 to 3 minutes\n
Add the shredded chicken. Stir and cook for 1 minute\n
Add the hot dog. Quickly stir and then pour the water used to boil the chicken. Also pour the remaining water. Let boil\n
Add the Knorr Chicken Cube. Stir. Cover and cook for 3 to 5 minutes\n
Put the elbow macaroni in the pot. Cook for 10 minutes\n
Add the cabbage. Stir and cook for 3 to 5 minutes. (Note: you can add more water if needed)\n
Pour the evaporated milk. Stir, let boil, cover and cook for another 3 minutes\n
Add salt and ground black pepper to taste\n
Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve\n
Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="h">
    Chicken Inasal
</string>
    <string name="h1">
"5pcs chicken leg quarter

For Marinade
4tbsp Knorr Liquid Seasoning
5thumbs ginger crushed
6cloves garlic crushed
1/2cup white vinegar
2cups lemon or lime soda
2stalks lemongrass

For Basting Sauce
1/2cup annatto seeds
4tbsp cooking oil
1/4tsp turmeric powder
1/2cup margarine
1/2pc lime"
    </string>
    <string name="h2">
        Chop the lemongrass and crush. Combine all marinade ingredients in a large bowl. Stir and let it stay for 10 minutes\n
Arrange chicken in large resealable bags. Use more bags if needed. Pour marinade into each bag equally. Push the air out of the bag and seal. Marinate overnight inside the refrigerator\n
Prepare the basting sauce by making annatto oil. Combine annatto seeds and 4 tablespoons cooking oil in a saucepan. Heat and continue to cook until the oil sizzles. Turn the heat off and stir until the oil turns red. Filter the oil from the seed\n
Combine annato oil with margarine, turmeric powder, and lime. You may also add some salt preferred\n
Heat-up the grill. Start grilling the chicken pieces for 2 minutes, and then turnover to grill the opposite side\n
        Brush basting sauce everytime the chicken is flipped. Do this using medium heat to prevent the skin from burning. If the heat is uncontrollable, remove skin before grilling to prevent it from burning. (Note: The chicken is cooked when the internal temperature is at least 165F)\n
Arrange your chicken inasal on a plate and serve with your favorite dipping sauce. Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="i">
       Kalderetang Manok
    </string>
    <string name="i1">
"2lbs chicken cut into pieces
1pc Knorr Chicken Cube
2pcs carrots wedged
2pcs potato cubed
8oz tomato sauce
2pcs bell pepper sliced
4tbsp liver spread
1pc tomato cubed
3pcs chili pepper chopped
1pc onion chopped
3cloves garlic crushed
3tbsp cheddar cheese grated
1and ½ cups water
4tbsp cooking oil"

    </string>
    <string name="i2">
Start by pan-frying the potato and carrots. Heat oil in a pan. Add potato. Fry each side for 1 minute. Remove from the pan and put in a bowl lined with paper towel. Set aside. Do the same thing with the carrots\n
Using the remaining oil, fry the chicken for 1 ½ minutes per side. Remove from the pan. Set aside\n
Saute onion and garlic. Add tomato. Continue to saute while stirring until tomato and onion softens\n
Add chicken and pour-in tomato sauce and water. Let boil\n
Stir and then add Knorr Chicken Cube and chili pepper. Cover the pan. Cook between low to medium heat for 15 minutes\n
Turn the chicken pieces over to equally cook the opposite side. Add liver spread. Stir. Cover and cook for 20 minutes\n
Add bell peppers and cheese. Cook for 3 minutes\n
Put the carrots and potatoes into the pan. Continue to cook for 5 to 7 minutes\n
Season with salt and ground black pepper\n
        Serve. Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="j">
        Lechon Manok
    </string>
    <string name="j1">
        "2to 3 lbs. whole chicken

For Marinade
4thumbs ginger crushed
5cloves garlic crushed
1medium red onion sliced
5pcs dried bay leaves crumbled
1stalk lemongrass bottom part crushed
1tsp coarse sea salt
1/4tsp ground black pepper
1and ¾ cups 7-up

For Stuffing
1stalk crushed lemongrass tanglad
2bunches of green onions dahon ng sibuyas"
    </string>
    <string name="j2">
        In a large bowl, combine all the marinade ingredients. Mix well\n
Place the chicken inside a large re-sealable bag. Pour the marinade in the bag with the chicken. Put the onion and lemongrass inside the cavity. Seal and refrigerate overnight\n
Remove the chicken from the bag and then stuff with fresh lemongrass and green onion\n
Prepare to roast the chicken on the grill by skewering the entire fowl on a spit and secure both sides with a grill fork\n
Spit-roast (or i-litson in Tagalog) for 2 ½ to 3 hours or until the chicken is done\n
Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with lechon manok sauce and atchara\n
Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="k">Pinaupong Manok</string>
    <string name="k1">
"1whole dressed chicken cleaned
1bunch lemongrass
1bunch leeks or green onions
1/2tsp ground black pepper
2to 3 cups coarse see salt
banana leaf"
</string>
    <string name="k2">
        Rub 3 tablespoons of salt and 1/2 teaspoon ground black pepper all over the chicken. Make sure that you also rub the seasonings in the chicken cavity for optimal flavor. Let it stay for 15 minutes\n
Stuff the lemongrass and leeks inside the chicken\n
Arrange the remaining salt on the cooking pot by spreading it to cover space\n
Place the banana leaf on top of the salt\n
Place the chicken over the banana leaf. Note: I use a small can of tomato sauce to help the chicken securely sit. Simply insert the can in the cavity\n
Turn the heat on to medium and steam for 80 to 90 minutes\n
Remove the chicken from the cooking pot and transfer to a serving plate\n
Serve with a dipping sauce composed of fish sauce and lemon or calamansi\n
Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="l">
        Adobong Manok na may Pinya
    </string>
    <string name="l1">
"1kg chicken parts, cut into serving portions
2tbsp crushed garlic
3tbsp del monte red cane vinegar
2tbsp soy sauce
1/4 cup oil, for frying
1pouch del monte pineapple tidbits (200g), drained, reserve syrup
1/4cup crushed and fried garlic"
    </string>
    <string name="l2">
        Marinate chicken for 30 minutes. Drain and reserve marinade\n
Fry chicken in oil until golden brown\n
Combine chicken with marinade then simmer until chicken is tender. Add del monte Pineapple Tidbits. Top with fried garlic\n
Serve. Enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="n">
    Sinampalukang Manok
</string>
    <string name="n1">
"2lbs chicken cut into serving pieces
3/4cups tamarind flower buds or tamarind leaves
1large red onion
4pcs long green pepper siding pansigang
3thumbs ginger sliced
4cloves garlic crushed
1pc 20g Knorr Sinigang sa Sampaloc Mix, original
1pc knorr Chicken Cube
3tbsp fish sauce
6cups water"
    </string>

    <string name="n2">
        Heat cooking pot and then sear the chicken. Continue to cook until most of the chicken fat are extracted\n
Remove the chicken from the pot. Set aside\n
Using the extracted oil, sauce garlic, onion, and ginger\n
Once the onion becomes soft, add the chicken back to the pot\n
Pour water. Let boil. Seal the tamarind flower buds in a cheesecloth and tie using a kitchen twine\n
Add the cheese cloth with tamarind flower buds in the pot. Stir\n
Add Knorr chicken cube and long green pepper. Cover the pot. Cook in medium heat until the chicken gets tender\n
Remove the tamarind flower buds. Add Knorr Singing Mix. Stir\n
Add fish sauce. Cook for 5 minutes\n
Transfer to a serving plate. Serve\n
Share and enjoy\n
    </string>

    <!-->  END
            END
            END
            END
            END
            END
            END
            </!-->


    <string name="t2">
        Sinigang na Baboy
    </string>
    <string name="e2">
"2lbs pork belly or buto-buto
1bunch spinach or kang-kong
3tbsp fish sauce
12pcs string beans sitaw, cut in 2 inch length
2pcs tomato quartered
3pcs chili or banana pepper
1tbsp cooking oil
2quarts water
1pc onion sliced
2pcs taro gabi, quartered
1pack Sinigang Mix good for 2 liters water"

    </string>
    <string name="tr1">
        Heat the pot and put-in the cooking oil\n
Sauté the onion until its layers separate from each other\n
Add the pork belly and cook until outer part turns light brown\n
Put-in the fish sauce and mix with the ingredients\n
Pour the water and bring to a boil\n
Add the taro and tomatoes then simmer for 40 minutes or until pork is tender\n
Put-in the sinigang mix and chili\n
Add the string beans (and other vegetables if there are any) and simmer for 5 to 8 minutes\n
Put-in the spinach, turn off the heat, and cover the pot. Let the spinach cook using the remaining heat in the pot\n
Serve hot. Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="a">
        Bicol Express
    </string>
    <string name="a1">
"1kg pork belly cut into cubes
1cup finger chilies siling haba, sliced
1cup string beans cut into 2-inch pcs
4cloves garlic sliced
1pc onion sliced
4pcs red chili peppers chopped
1tbsp ginger sliced
2tbsp shrimp paste alamang
salt and pepper to taste
1and ½ cups coconut milk
1cup coconut cream kakang gata
1cup water
1tbsp cooking oil"
    </string>
    <string name="a2">
        In a preheated pan, heat cooking oil\n
Add garlic, ginger, and onion. Sauté until fragrant\n
Add pork. Cook while stirring occasionally until light brown\n
Add shrimp paste. Stir and cook for about 2 minutes\n
Add the coconut milk, water, and red chili peppers. Simmer for about 30 minutes or until pork is tender\n
Add the coconut cream and simmer until the liquid thickens\n
Add string beans and finger chilies. Cook while stirring regularly for about 2 minutes\n
Season with salt and pepper. Stir well\n
Remove from heat. Transfer to a serving bowl\n
Serve while hot with steamed rice. Enjoy your Bicol Express\n
    </string>


    <string name="m">
        Crispy Pork Bagnet
    </string>
    <string name="m1">
"3lbs pork belly
2tbsp white vinegar
2tbsp salt
2bunches lemongrass
1tbsp whole peppercorn
1onion
8cups water
6cloves garlic
3pcs laurel leaves
6cups cooking oil"
</string>
    <string name="m2">
        Preheat oven to 175F\n
Pour water into a pressure cooker. Add lemongrass, salt, whole peppercorn, and onion. Let boil\n
Add pork belly. Boil for 3 minutes. Cover the pressure cooker. Cook for 15 minutes\n
Let the pressure out completely Put the pork belly on a clean plate and let it cool-down for 10 minutes. Season the meat part with salt and ground black pepper. Turn it upside down and season the skin part with salt\n
Wrap the sides of the pork with an aluminum foil and then rub vinegar on the skin part\n
Bake it for 2 ½ hours to dehydrate the skin\n
Remove the pork from the oven. Set aside\n
Heat oil in a wide wok. Once the oil gets hot, add garlic and laurel leaves. Cook until the garlic floats. Remove the garlic and leaves afterwards using a strainer\n
Arrange a slab of pork belly over a skimmer. Pour hot oil over it using a ladle. Do this step until a crackling texture is formed on the skin. Perform the same steps until all the pork are done\n
Arrange on a serving plate. Serve with your favorite dipping sauce. Share and enjoy\n

    </string>


    <string name="o">
        Creamy Pork and Mushrooms
    </string>
    <string name="o1">
        "For Pork Chops
5pcs large pieces pork shoulder chops, about 1” thick cut in half
salt
freshly ground black pepper
oil

For Creamy Mushroom Gravy
3cups rich beef/pork stock
250g button mushrooms, sliced
1/2cup cream
1/3cup flour
1/3cup butter
1pc white onion, finely chopped
4cloves garlic, minced
handful of parsley, chopped
freshly ground black pepper
salt
oil"

    </string>
    <string name="o2">
        In a heavy pan add oil then pan fry pork shoulder chops for 4-5 minutes on each side in medium heat until pork is cooked through.  Remove pork from the pan then set it aside\n
Using the same pan, add and cook mushrooms for 2 minutes, remove from the pan then set it aside\n
Add the butter and melt in low heat. Sauté garlic and onions until onions are soft\n
Add flour then cook until it forms a roux\n
Gradually add 3 cups of beef stock while continuously mixing\n
Add cream, continue to cook until it becomes a smooth sauce\n
Add the mushrooms and the pork back into the pan then simmer in low heat of for 5 minutes. Season with salt and freshly ground black pepper\n
Remove from heat, garnish with chopped parsley, let it stand for 5 minutes to let the mushroom sauce to penetrate into the pork chops then serve\n

    </string>


    <string name="p">Dinakdakang Baboy</string>
    <string name="p1">
"2lbs. liempo pork belly
1/2cup Lady’s Choice Mayonnaise
3tbsp Knorr Liquid Seasoning
2to 3 pcs lime or 5 to 6 pieces calamansi
2pcs red onion sliced into thin pieces
10pcs Thai chili peppers chopped
3pcs long green pepper sliced
1tsp onion powder optional
salt and ground black pepper to taste
1and ½ quarts water"
</string>
    <string name="p2">
        Boil water in a cooking pot\n
Add pork belly. Cover and continue to boil in medium heat for 30 to 35 minutes\n
Remove the pork belly from the pot. Let it cool. Note: you may use the pork stock (water used to boil liempo) to cook other dishes\n
Rub 1 teaspoon salt and ½ teaspoon ground black pepper over the pork belly. Let it stay for 10 minutes\n
Heat-up the grill. Grill each side for a total of 6 minutes. Note: I usually grill one side for 2 minutes, turn the belly over and grill the opposite side for the same time. The process is repeated 2 to 3 times. This will prevent the pork belly from being burnt\n
Slice the pork belly into thin pieces and arrange in a large mixing bowl\n
Prepare the dressing by combining mayonnaise, Knorr Liquid Seasoning, lime juice, and onion powder in a small bowl. Stir until well blended. Set aside\n
Put the onion and chili peppers on the bowl with the sliced pork belly. Toss\n
Add the dressing. Continue to toss until well blended. Add Salt and pepper to taste\n
Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve\n
Share and enjoy\n

    </string>


    <string name="q">
        Dinuguang Baboy
    </string>
    <string name="q1">
"2lbs pork shoulder cubed
1and 1/4 cups pork blood
1pc Knorr Pork Cube
4pcs long peppers
2pcs onion chopped
6cloves garlic minced
2cups water
3/4cup white vinegar
3pcs dried bay leaves
3tbsp cooking oil
1tbsp granulated white sugar
salt and ground black pepper to taste"
    </string>
    <string name="q2">
        Heat oil in a cooking pot
Saute onion for 30 seconds. Add garlic. Continue to cook until onion softens\n
Add pork. Saute for 3 to 5 minutes\n
Pour water. Let boil. Add bay leaves and vinegar. Let the liquid re-boil\n
Add Knorr Pork Cube. Stir. Cover and simmer for 1 hour. Note: add water as needed\n
Add long green peppers and pour pork blood into the pot. Stir. Continue to cook between low to medium heat for 15 minutes while stirring every 3 minutes\n
Add sugar and season with salt and ground black pepper\n
Transfer to a serving bowl. Enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="r">
     Kare-Kare ala Bagnet
    </string>
    <string name="r1">
"4lbs. pork belly
5cups water
3tbsp salt
3cups cooking oil
1/2cup bagoong alamang
2bunches pechay
1pc eggplant sliced
12pcs string beans
1cup banana blossoms sliced

For Kare-Kare Sauce
2 cups roasted peanuts
1 piece Knorr Pork Cube
1/2 cup annatto seeds
1 piece onion chopped
3 cloves garlic minced
1 ½ tablespoons toasted rice powder
2 cups water
3 tablespoons cooking oil"


</string>
    <string name="r2">
        Prepare the pork. Boil water in a large cooking pot. Add pork. Continue boiling for 35 minutes. Remove the pork from the pot and let it cook down. Rub salt all over and let it stay for 5 minutes\n
Heat oil in a large pan. Once the oil gets really hot, fry the pork belly (skin side down). Note: BE CAREFUL! Splash 1 1/2 tablespoons of water on the oil every 3 minutes or until the skin gets golden brown and very crispy\n
Flip the pork and continue frying until the opposite side turns golden brown. Remove pork from the cooking pot and place it over a wire rack to let the excess oil drip. Set aside\n
Start to make the sauce. Grind the peanuts using a food processor until the texture becomes paste-like. Set aside\n
Make annatto water by soaking annatto seeds in hot water for 5 minutes. Constantly stir until the water turns deep orange. Filter the water using a kitchen strainer. You may discard the seeds afterwards. Set aside\n
      Heat oil in a pan. Saute garlic and onion. Once the onion softens, add the peanut paste. Stir and cook for 1 minute\n
Pour water and then stir until the mixture becomes smooth. Let the liquid boil\n
Add Knorr Pork Cube and annatto water. Cover and continue cooking for 3 minutes. Remove the cover and cook until the mixture reduces to your desired consistency. Add toasted rice powder. Mix well. Turn off the heat. Make sure to cover the pot to keep the sauce warm\n
Cook the vegetables by steaming. Arrange string bean, banana blossom, and eggplant on a steamer. Steam for 5 minutes. Add pechay and continue steaming for 2 to 3 minutes\n
Assemble your crispy kare-kare by combining the sauce, steamed vegetables, and crispy pork in one plate. Serve with rice and bagoong alamang. Share and enjoy\n

    </string>


    <string name="s">
        Lechon Paksiw
    </string>
    <string name="s1">
"2lbs roasted pork preferably leftovers
3laurel leaves
salt to taste

For Lechon Sauce
5oz pork liver sliced
1Knorr Pork cube
5tbsp white vinegar
7tbsp dark brown sugar
1/2tsp ground black pepper
1onion, chopped
1head garlic, crushed
2and ½ cups water
1tbsp soy sauce
3tbsp breadcrumbs
3tsbp cooking oil"
    </string>
    <string name="s2">
        Heat oil in a pan. Add the pork liver. Fry until color turns brown\n
Remove the liver from the pot and place inside the blender. Add water. Puree the mixture. Set aside\n
Using the remaining oil, sauté garlic and onion until the latter softens\n
Pour the liver puree. Let boil\n
Add Knorr Pork Cube, soy sauce, vinegar, and ground black pepper. Let the mixture boil. Stir\n
Add brown sugar and breadcrumbs. Turn the heat off and pour the entire mixture back into the blender. Puree for 1 minute\n
Pour the puree back into the cooking pot. Let it boil\n
Add laurel leaves and roasted pork. Cover the pan. Continue cooking in a low heat setting for 40 minutes\n
Season with salt as needed\n
Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve warm. Share and enjoy with rice\n
    </string>


    <string name="u">
        Binagoongang Baboy
    </string>
    <string name="u1">
        "2lbs pork belly cut into cubes
2pcs tomato cubed
1pc Chinese eggplant sliced
3and ½ cups pork stock
3tbsp white vinegar
4tbsp bagoong alamang
1pc onion chopped
3cloves garlic chopped
2tsp granulated white sugar
1/8tsp ground black pepper
3tbsp cooking oil"
    </string>
    <string name="u2">
        Heat oil in a cooking pot\n
Saute onion, garlic, and tomato. Once the onion becomes soft, add the pork belly. Cook until the belly turns light brown\n
Add shrimp paste (bagoong alamang). Stir. Cook for 5 minutes\n
Pour vinegar. Let the mixture boil. Stir and cook for 2 minutes\n
Pour the pork stock into the pot. Cover and let boil. Adjust the heat to medium and continue to cook for 40 minutes or until the pork gets tender. (Note: add water or pork stock as needed)\n
Add eggplant. Stir. Cover the pot and cook for 3 minutes\n
Season with sugar and ground black pepper\n
Transfer to a serving plate. Serve. Share and enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="v">
        Sisig Kapampangan
    </string>
    <string name="v1">
"1and ½lbs pork belly boiled for 1 hour
1/2cup Lady’s Choice Mayonnaise
2pcs onion chopped
4pcs Thai chili pepper chopped
2pcs long green pepper chopped
16g Knorr SavorRich Pork equivalent to 1 sachet
1/2tsp ground black pepper
2tbsp soy sauce
1/4cup margarine
2cups cooking oil"

    </string>
    <string name="v2">
        Heat oil in a deep cooking pot or deep fryer. Fry the boiled pork belly until golden brown and crispy. Chop the crispy pork belly into small pieces. Set aside\n
Heat half of the margarine in a pan. Sauté half of the onions until soft. Add chopped pork. Saute for 30 seconds\n
Add Knorr SavorRich. Stir and then add chili peppers and season with ground black pepper and soy sauce. Cook for 1 minute\n
Add Lady’s Choice Mayonnaise. Stir and add remaining onion. Set aside\n
Heat a metal plate (sizzling plate) on a stovetop. Melt remaining margarine. Transfer the crispy pork sisig into the metal plate. Let it stay for 30 seconds\n
Serve with warm rice and your favorite beverage. Enjoy\n
    </string>


    <string name="w">
        Menudong Baboy
    </string>
    <string name="w1">
"2lbs pork
1/4lb pig liver
1cup potatoes diced
1pc carrot cubed
1/2cup soy sauce
1/2pc lemon
1pc onion chopped
3cloves garlic minced
1tsp sugar
3/4cup tomato sauce
1cup water
4pcs hotdogs sliced diagonally
2tbsp cooking oil
2to 3 pcs dried bay leaves
salt and pepper to taste"

    </string>
    <string name="w2">
        Combine pork, soysauce, and lemon in a bowl. Marinate for at least 1 hour\n
Heat oil in a pan. Saute garlic and onion\n
Add the marinated pork. Cook for 5 to 7 minutes\n
Pour in tomato sauce and water and then add the bay leaves.Let boil and simmer for 30 minutes to an hour depending on the toughness of the pork. Note: Add water as necessary\n
Add-in the liver and hot dogs.Cook for 5 minutes\n
Put-in potatoes, carrots, sugar,salt, and pepper. Stir and cook for 8 to 12 minutes\n
Serve. Share and enjoy\n

    </string>


    <string name="x">
        Pork Humba
    </string>
    <string name="x1">
"4lbs pork belly cubed
1pc Knorr Pork Cube
3cups clear soft drink
1cup water as needed
2oz banana blossoms
2tbsp salted black beans
3tbsp white vinegar
1/2cup soy sauce
1pc onion chopped
2tbsp brown sugar
6cloves garlic crushed and chopped
1/2tsp crushed peppercorn"

    </string>
    <string name="x2">
        Heat a wok or pan. Sear pork belly until it turns brown and enough oil gets extracted from the fat. Remove the pork from the wok. Set aside\n
Heat around 3 tablespoons of oil. Sauté garlic and onion until the onion softens\n
Add the pork back into the wok and pour-in soy sauce. Sauté for 1 minute\n
Add vinegar. Continue sautéing until liquid dries-up\n
Pour clear soft drinks into the wok. Cover and let boil\n
Add crushed peppercorn. Adjust heat to low. Continue boiling for 35 minutes\n
Add banana blossoms and salted black beans. Cover the wok and continue cooking until the pork gets tender. Note: you can add water if needed\n
Add brown sugar. Stir. Cook for 1 minute\n
Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with warm rice\n
Share and enjoy\n

    </string>


    <string name="open" />
    <string name="close" />
    <string name="logout" />


</resources>
